<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Script>
  <Scene id="scene_1_6" pageStart="28" pageEnd="30" act="Act 1: The Inciting Incident"
    title="Stella's Home" description="Stella and Tyson watch a news report on the dockworkers">
    <Page number="28">
      <StageDirection>STELLA is now at home with TYSON, both on their laptops. The TV is on in the
        background.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>So ... Tony only asked for a dollar for licking the toilet?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Yeah. And then we all have detention for the rest of the week.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Why do you have detention though? You didn't lick the toilet. Did you?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>No!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>I'm proud of you.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="29">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line> Shut up. Miss Duane said that I should have stood up and said it was a bad idea. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>I wouldn't take Miss Duane too seriously. She misspelled 'conduct' on my report card
          when she taught me. And “Tyson.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I don't think it's fair though. I'm being punished because Tony is gross.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Correct. You are. You're learning that things are unfair, and life is unfair. You're
          really growing up today. So proud.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TV</Speaker>
        <Line>We now go live to Moon Beach, where two men reported missing yesterday have
          been found dead, two kilometres from where they were last seen at their place of work at
          the
          dockyards.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Oh no.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TV</Speaker>
        <Line> We regret to advise that we cannot show you any disturbing images at this
          time, as the bodies are reported to be severely disfigured. One bystander is quoted as
          saying 'they look mutated and stuff? 'I threw up in my mouth a little' and 'It's pretty
          awesome: We spoke to some of the men's colleagues earlier, before they too died
          suspiciously.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>Some of the DOCKWORKERS from before being interviewed.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Line>Just goes to show you never know when it's your time, hey?</Line>
        <Line>One minute you're drinking energy drink that so called experts call toxic and the next
          ...</Line>
        <Line>Death sounds.</Line>
        <Line>But they died doing what they loved, you know?</Line>
        <Line>Geeing each other up.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>They raise cans of the drinks to sip.</StageDirection>
    </Page>
    <Page number="30">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>REPORTER</Speaker>
        <Line>Aren't those the same drinks?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Line>Oh no. Worst gee up.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TV</Speaker>
        <Line>To see the full, uncut footage, join us at 11 for our Sexy News
          Bulletin, or follow me on Twitter for all of the uncut action.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Ugh. Who watches the news on TV anymore?</Line>
        <InlineDirection>He shuts it off.</InlineDirection>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Ty, I was watching that!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Stick to podcasts, you little weirdo. News is for boomers. Get to bed.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>
        They leave. In the shadows, a silhouette of an octopus appears, crawling in the middle of a
        street. A can of energy drink lies at the side of the road. The octopus continues to crawl,
        until he touches some of the spilled liquid. Suddenly, he shakes and begins to grow larger
        and more muscular, until he is the size of a fully grown man. He raises his arms and roars.</StageDirection>
    </Page>
  </Scene>
</Script>