<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Script>
  <Scene id="scene_1_4" pageStart="21" pageEnd="23" act="Act 1: The Inciting Incident" title="Assembly" description="Mr. Fowler addresses the school; SRC discusses the Pre-formal">
    <Page number="21">
      <StageDirection>The bell rings again. Whatever song it is, stick with it for the rest of the show. We're in Assembly. MR FOWLER is addressing the students.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>— and as we welcome all of you back for another exciting year, a reminder that the demountables are out of bounds until the snake nests are dealt with. Do not approach the snakes. Also, I can't believe that I need to address this —</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>One of the kids is talking.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>I'll wait.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>This is eating into your lunch time everyone.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>I need to remind students not to make bets on licking toilets. Some of our Grade Tens who should know/ better</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>A KID</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>KID</Speaker>
        <Line>Tonksie!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>Than to be licking toilets.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>Some laughter.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>Oh you all think that's funny? Getting on your knees and treating a toilet like a lollipop? In a 30 degree tin shed thats filthy with old urine? Hot porcelain? That's funny? Well laugh it up.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>If the laughter continues:</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>I'll wait again. Your time, everyone. Not mine. Now I won't see it happen again. And now, I'd like to invite the SRC representatives, Madison, Maddison and Madyson who'll be giving a short reminder on the Year 10 pre-formal.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>The SRC take the podium. Scattered applause. The girls are very polished presenters.</StageDirection>
    </Page>
    <Page number="22">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADISON</Speaker>
        <Line>Welcome everyone to 2020. We made it. Wow. Whod have thought? For those of you who don't know me, my name is Madison, and It's my pleasure to be serving as your President of the SRC!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>She holds for an applause she'll never hear.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADISON</Speaker>
        <Line>Also, this is Maddison and Madyson with a Y.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>BOTH</Speaker>
        <Line>MADDISON</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADDISON</Speaker>
        <Line>We've got a packed agenda coming up this year with moving toward plastic free packaging in the canteen and a second clothing donation drive this Wednesday!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Save the turtles guys!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADDISON</Speaker>
        <Line>[sotto] | need you to take a step back.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Sorry.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADDISON</Speaker>
        <Line>And we haven't even begun to talk about the event of the school calendar, the Year 10 Pre-formal! Here to tell you more is Madyson with a Y!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Thanks, Maddie.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADDISON</Speaker>
        <Line>Maddison.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Good morning students and teachers. At the Royal Wedding to her Prince Harry, Meghan Markle disrupted tradition, and chose to carve a stronger path for herself and upsetting a system by marrying into it. And we hope you'll embrace the same spirit of rebellion and make bold choices at the event of the school calendar ...</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADISON</Speaker>
        <Line>Move over, HPV vaccines!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>ALL 3</Speaker>
        <Line>The Year 10 Pre-Formal!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="23">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADDISON</Speaker>
        <Line>With this year's theme, we decided to take things out of the quad and... Under The Sea.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>But while the SRC will be in charge of planning, creative direction, hosting, most of the work, we really want you to feel empowered to make this your night. But there are some notes before we can let you start planning. In order to stay on the aesthetic the following colour dresses are banned: White. Off White.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADISON</Speaker>
        <Line>The colour, not the label. Haha.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADDISON</Speaker>
        <Line>Periwinkle. Cyan.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>Okay, that's enough. Thank you girls.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>More scattered applause.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>Alright, thank you everyone, now off to your next period please. Move responsibly.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
  </Scene>
</Script>