<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Script>
  <Scene id="scene_1_1" pageStart="10" pageEnd="12" act="Act 1: The Inciting Incident" title="Prologue" description="Introduction of the STORYTELLERS and the ocean">
    <Page number="10">
      <StageDirection>Darkness. A fog has settled across the floor as STORYTELLERS appear onstage one by one, in very neat black suits, ties. All of them should all feel connected — like multiple parts of a kaleidoscope.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STORYTELLERS</Speaker>
        <Line>I want you to consider for the moment the 71 percent of our planet that is cut off from us.</Line>
        <Line>The part of our home that you may be able to see, maybe even step into. But the part of our home and mine that we can never fully know.</Line>
        <Line>The ocean.</Line>
        <Line>This is the ocean. This is the surface, where I'm standing right now.</Line>
        <Line>If I take a step down into the deep with the ocean floor there...</Line>
        <InlineDirection>They step forward.</InlineDirection>
        <Line>The pressure builds. The water above pushes you down with gravity in a push and pull of nature.</Line>
        <Line>Among humans, the smart and the scared will only dive so far before the ocean collapses their lungs and squeezes their bodies.About here.</Line>
        <InlineDirection>They take a smaller step.</InlineDirection>
        <Line>The rest below us is largely unknown. There isn't much for us there but the darkness and the creatures that drift in the great shadows.</Line>
        <Line>This is why you should fear the ocean. The things that go bump in the night are the easy explanations.</Line>
        <Line>A trick of the mind.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="12">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STORYTELLERS</Speaker>
        <Line>The walls in your house cooling down, expanding and compressing with temperature fluctuations.</Line>
        <Line>It's not the things that go bump in the night that you should fear.</Line>
        <Line>It's the things that don't bump at all.</Line>
        <Line>And on the floor of the ocean where creatures live in perpetual darkness, fighting for scraps that descend from the surface for an age, they only wait.</Line>
        <Line>For it's only a matter of time before they decide to rise.</Line>
        <Line>This is a story that starts with the void. A void that is very much staring back.</Line>
        <Line>Also, we'll do the Cha Cha Slide.</Line>
        <Line>Let's begin.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
  </Scene>
</Script>