<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Script>
	<Scene id="scene_4_1" pageStart="52" pageEnd="54" act="Act 4: The Darkest Night" title="The Dance"
 description="Greg stalks and threatens Stella during the Cha Cha Slide">
		<Page number="52">
			<StageDirection>It’s going off in the hall as the Formal is in full swing. MISS DUANE is
  playing the music from her phone. Everyone is dancing is formation. PRIYA is sitting on the
  side.</StageDirection>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>Madison</Speaker>
				<Line>Hiiii everyone, just a reminder that the photobooth only holds eight people, so just
   take turns or have less friends! Have a good night everyone! You'll remember this night
   for the rest of your lives.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
				<Line>I hope not.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<StageDirection>STELLA enters.</StageDirection>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
				<Line>Have you seen TOny?</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
		</Page>
		<Page number="53">
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>No, I thought he was with you?</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
				<Line>You don't think...</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>I don't want to.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
				<Line>I'll go and look for him. Stay here in case he turns up, okay? Text me if you need me.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<StageDirection>She leaves.</StageDirection>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>No wait! I'll come with you!</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<StageDirection>She is stopped by MADYSON.</StageDirection>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>MADYSON</Speaker>
				<Line>Everybody on the D floor now! That means you!</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>No, I have to go!</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<StageDirection>MISS DUANE takes the mic</StageDirection>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
				<Line>Make the most of tonight, everyone, it’s all uphill from here. One day you might DJ a school dance. But for now, here's a song you might remember. </Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<StageDirection>The Cha Cha Slide. STELLA tries to escape, but has no choice but to dance with
  everybody else. As the song continues, it gets more sinister as GREG appears in the
  darkness, With each strobe flash, each criss cross, he inches closer and closer to STELLA as
  she senses with horror that he is near. He ends the song right behind her. Everybody cheers
  as the song ends, and moves into a slow dance. Everybody pairs up as STELLA pleads for
  someone, anyone else to dance with. GREG grabs her and pulls her in. For everyone else, this
  is romantic. For her, it's bone chilling.</StageDirection>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>Why me?</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
				<Line>I don't know what you mean.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
		</Page>
		<Page number="54">
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>Why did you pick me? Why are you doing this to me?</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
				<Line>It's simple.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>Why?</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
				<Line>Because I can. I'm going to take your house and your family and destroy them all. And
   I'm going to make you watch, Because you're just a nothing human kid and you can do
   nothing to stop me. You're weak. You told me yourself. You're not special. You have such a
   long life of misery ahead of you. I'm doing you a favour by tearing it down. And I will.
   Piece by piece. You asked me if I can do anything special, do you remember? I have many
   abilities, Stella. There are so many things that I can do. And I will do them all to you.
   And nobody will help you. Nobody will care, The entire world will let me win.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>You're a monster.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
				<Line>I know you are, but what am I?</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>I won't do it.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
				<Line>I know you are, but what am I?</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>You're not funny.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
				<Line>I know you are, but what am I?</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>You're horrible.</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
				<Line>I know you are, but what am I?</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<DialogueBlock>
				<Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
				<Line>Leave me alone!</Line>
			</DialogueBlock>
			<StageDirection>She shoves him as the music cuts. Everyone stares as GREG calculates his next
  move... and runs away. Everyone at the dance looks at STELLA with disgust as the dance melts
  away.</StageDirection>
		</Page>
	</Scene>
</Script>