<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Script>
  <Scene id="scene_5_6" pageStart="75" pageEnd="82" act="Act 5: The Showdown" title="The Flagpole"
    description="The final battle between Stella and Squish">
    <Page number="75">
      <SceneHeading>The Flagpole</SceneHeading>
      <StageDirection>FRIDAY, 2:55PM The flagpole. SQUISH is punching a brick wall. All of the kids
        are gathered. Suddenly, the lights dim. Everything is highly stylised from this point.
        Smoke, flashing lights. It is STELLA. She is fitted in armour fashioned from random sports
        goods, kitchen wear, and other household items, but it looks rad. She has a small bumbag
        across her body. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>SQUISH</Speaker>
        <Line>Ready to die, brah?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>We know your plans, Squish. We know there are others like you. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="76">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>SQUISH</Speaker>
        <Line>Doesn't matter. We're smarter than you, we're stronger than you. And I'm going to show
          you right now why. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>He pulls two long, neon pink whips out of his backpack. He begins swinging
        them around. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>What are they?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>SQUISH</Speaker>
        <Line>Jellyfish stingers. I ripped them straight off this pussy swimming by this morning
          just for you. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>OCTOPUSES ACTUALLY DO THIS. IT'S MESSED UP. Ready?</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Ready. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>The school bell rings. It's three o'clock. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>ALL</Speaker>
        <Line>FILIMIGGGGGHHHHHTTTT!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>They run straight at each other. SQUISH's whips wrap around STELLA' armour,
        tangling her. SQUISH begins hauling her toward him, but as he is in reach, she headbutts
        him. He lets go, and she frees herself. It's a vicious scuffle, trading punches and kicks.
        It's like a Kaiju film — lots of grappling between two titans. STELLA lands a solid punch on
        SQUISH 's face, and sends him back. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Priya, I don't feel so good. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>I told you not to eat sugar!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>SQUISH retreats to his backpack and grabs a water bomb filled with a dark
        liquid. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>SQUISH</Speaker>
        <Line>Get some ink up ya!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>SQUISH throws the balloon. Ink splatters across STELLA' helmet, blinding her.
        SQUISH jumps on her back and latches on. She tries to shake him off, but his suckers have
        attached to her. STELLA runs back into the pole. It bends, SQUISH falls off, STELLA rips off
        her helmet. She can see again. She turns around and SQUISH lands a punch straight to the
        stomach, winding her. It looks bad. PRIYA is horrified, TONY is eating a Killer Python and
        shivering. </StageDirection>
    </Page>
    <Page number="77">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>No! Get up, Stella! You have to get up! Tony, we have to do something!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Um ... I don't know —</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Think!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>So... much ... sugar. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>SQUISH readies the knockout punch. TONY takes another bite of the Killer
        Python. He shakes violently. FRANCINE suddenly appears on her bike. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>Now, Tony! Do it! Just like we talked about!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>I don't know if I can. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>You have to! I believe in you! Do it!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>TONY eats the last part of the Killer Python. He seizures. -PRIYA Tony!</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>That was my name once. Now I am eternal. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>What?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>TONY shakes more violently as a booming sound rumbles in a crescendo to
        silence. Everything is beautiful, time slows almost to a stop around TONY. There is peaceful
        music. He gently brushes the hair out of STELLAS face. He wipes the ink off STELLA' helmet
        and places it back on her head. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>You're almost there, Tony. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="78">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>To where?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>To your part to play. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>I thought this was it. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>She needs to know what she's fighting for. You need to help her. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>What?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>You have to help her. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>You want me to take her place. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>I'm so sorry, Tony. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>I thought this was my chance to be something else. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>You will be. But you need to do this, Tony. I promise things will change, but you have
          to do this this one time. And they can't know how. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Nobody knows anyway. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>Are you ready?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>It's just like every other day. And nobody knows. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>Everything moves back to normal. SQUISH swings at TONY, landing a thunderous
        blow to his stomach. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>SQUISH</Speaker>
        <Line>What?!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>What just happened? Tony!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>SQUISH laughs and takes out his phone to take photos. </StageDirection>
    </Page>
    <Page number="79">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>SQUISH</Speaker>
        <Line>You feeling strong, my man? You think you can all just swim around in the ocean like
          you own it?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>But I don't swim —</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>SQUISH</Speaker>
        <Line>You humans want to behave like we do? Maybe I'll be a human boy for a bit. </Line>
        <Line>You're all so gross. You heard of tea bagging bruh? It's all the rage in private
          schools. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>SQUISH stands over TONY's face with his phone, ready to humiliate him. STELLA
        is struggling to get up. </StageDirection>
      <StageDirection>This'll be awesome when it's mailed to the TikTok or whatever you do. </StageDirection>
      <StageDirection>STELLA is furious, She ties her hair up and back. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Hey!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>SQUISH</Speaker>
        <Line>You're dead. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>She spits blood on the floor. With a gutteral venom</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I know you are. But what am I?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>SQUISH throws his phone down and takes a swing, he misses. STELLA unleashes
        hell on him, landing punch after punch. They continue to fight as the action crosses to
        THREE KIDS with a large scale model of a city. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>KID 1</Speaker>
        <Line>I now call to order the first Junior City Planners' meeting for the school year. And,
          might I add, no drop in members three years running. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>KID 2</Speaker>
        <Line>Eat it, Junior Accountants!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>KID 3</Speaker>
        <Line>And what better way to celebrate than a full scale model of Tokyo district, complete
          with the iconic Shibuya Crossing!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>It lights up. </StageDirection>
    </Page>
    <Page number="80">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>ALL</Speaker>
        <Line>Building a better tomorrow — today!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>STELLA and SQUISH suddenly crash through the model as they continue scuffling.
        The KIDS scatter, screaming. More fighting as the rest of the kids join the fight. THE GRADE
        7s appear, and attack. STELLA manages to rip off SQUISH® disguise, revealing a gross, giant
        octopus head. He looks terrifying. He roars. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>SQUISH</Speaker>
        <Line>Why won't you stay down?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I'll never stay down!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>STELLA reaches into the bum bag and pulls out firecrackers. She throws them on
        the ground, and they pop and flash. SQUISH screams. STELLA lands a punch square on SQUISHS
        face. Somehow in all of this, the entire cohort gets their hits in, including THE GRADE 7s.
        They overwhelm SQUISH as he is weakened. </StageDirection>
      <StageDirection>STELLA and SQUISH are at a standstill, ready to finish this. SQUISH tries to
        punch her, but STELLA goes low and grabs him around the waist. She lifts with all of her
        might. SQUISH goes high in the air, and STELLA holds him for a frozen moment. </StageDirection>
      <StageDirection>PRIYA is stunned. TONY is in a sugar coma. MISS DUANE is vaping at the school
        fence on the other side of the block, on her phone. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Jordan, hat on buddy. Won't say it again. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>Back to our action as STELLA slams SQUISH down to the ground. Flashing lights
        and stuff. SQUISH is flattened on the floor. STELLA is lying face down. She's not moving. </StageDirection>
    </Page>
    <Page number="81">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Oooooh we are in so much trouble. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>STELLA slowly picks herself up. The kids run over to her, shouting over the
        top of each other about how awesome the fight was. TONY catches a glimpse of FRANCINE, and
        goes over to her. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Did you see?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>I saw. You did it, Tony. You helped your friend. Tony, I meant what I said. Your life
          today, as it is. It won't always be this way. You have to believe me. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>How do you know?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>I don't know how. But I know you. And I know that you'll be fine. I hope we cross
          paths again someday. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>You're leaving?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>I am. There are others like him, and so there are other children to warn. My role
          isn't played out yet. But I'm afraid our time together has. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>But I don't even know your name. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>Well, you can't really pronounce it without a beak between your legs. You can just
          call me Francine. </Line>
        <Line>You're so much bigger than the world you are living in, Tony Tonks. Please remember
          that. I believe in you. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>She kisses him on the cheek and rides away on her bike. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>How can we ever repay you?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FRANCINE</Speaker>
        <Line>Stop throwing things in the ocean!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>She is gone. MISS DUANE enters. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>WHAT IS GOING ON?! Greg, you need to get up right now. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="82">
      <StageDirection>SQUISH doesn't move. She pokes him with her foot. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Greg?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Um ... I think Greg is gone, miss. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Priya, please. I'm disciplining. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Look at his face. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>She pushes his body with her foot, looking at his true face. </StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Oh god, it's like a bag of wet bread rolls. What is it?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>He wasn't who he said he was. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Ugh. He'd get along great with my ex. Well whatever he was, nobody else needs to know.
          None of us were here. I'm not losing my job over another body. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>Stella Bunt, I am so disappointed in you. I'd expect violent outbursts from
        her and pretty much anything from him, but from you? What do you have to say for yourself?</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Grade 10 is a big year. </Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>The STORYTELLERS from the prologue enter once more. </StageDirection>
    </Page>
  </Scene>
</Script>