<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Script>
  <Scene id="scene_2_4" pageStart="38" pageEnd="39" act="Act 2: The Rising Threat" title="PE Class"
    description="A vicious game of Dodgeball highlighting Greg's aggression">
    <Page number="38">
      <SceneHeading>PE Class</SceneHeading>
      <StageDirection>DODGEBALL</StageDirection>
      <StageDirection>The sound of a whistle. MR RIDGE, the PE Teacher has gathered the kids into
        teams. They're lined up to play. STELLA and GREG are on the same team.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>RIDGE</Speaker>
        <Line>Alright, now. There are some of you that still believe that Phys Ed is a cop out. That
          it doesn't prepare you for the real world out there. Well, let me just be the one to tell
          you that there is nothing'that prepares you more for the cruelty and indifference of the
          world than dodging balls in a game we like to call ... Dodgeball. The game is simple,
          everyone. Dodge the balls. You're hit, you're out. Work as a team. You ready?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>He blows the whistle. Music pumps, it's extreme. The team quickly gets
        whittled down until STELLA and GREG are the only two left on their team. GREG suddenly
        throws a ball at STELLA, hard.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>RIDGE</Speaker>
        <Line>38</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="39">
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>RIDGE</Speaker>
        <Line>Stella. You're out. Let's go mate. Quickly now!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>But he's on my team!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>RIDGE</Speaker>
        <Line>Don't argue with me madam. You know the rules. You get hit, you're out.</Line>
        <Line>Wouldn't be the first time balls hit her in the face.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>Snickers from some of the boys.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Hey! Six, you have to do something.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>RIDGE</Speaker>
        <Line>Well I'm trying to, Priya, but first we have to make sure this game is fair. Sit down,
          Stella. You're out.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>STELLA sighs and leaves the court. GREG beats the other team effortlessly. We
        should see a bit more of his vicious streak here.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>RIDGE</Speaker>
        <Line>Oof. You've got an arm, son. Good job. Alright everyone, showers and changed before
          next period. Stella. A word please.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>The other kids leave.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>RIDGE</Speaker>
        <Line>I hope you realise that I don't find it fun to have to stick to the rules all the
          time. It's nothing personal, but if I've learned one thing in my time as a PE teacher it's
          that the rules are there for a reason. Do you know why?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>No.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock>
        <Speaker>RIDGE</Speaker>
        <Line>To protect us all. Dodgeball might seem like a silly thing to be strict about, but
          take this lightly and the rest becomes a joke too, okay? Alright. Good talk. Off you go,
          love.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
  </Scene>
</Script>