<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Script>
  <Scene id="scene_5_1" pageStart="61" pageEnd="64" act="Act 5: The Showdown" title="The Classroom" description="A failed &quot;Talking Totem&quot; intervention">
    <Page number="61">
      <SceneHeading>The Classroom</SceneHeading>
      <StageDirection>STELLA appears in the classroom, where MISS DUANE and MR FOWLER are waiting.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>You wanted to see me?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Stella, have a seat please.</Line>
        <Line>What I am about to say, I want you to understand that I am saying it with no judgement, okay?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Yeah.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Good. Now, it has been brought to my attention that there are some people in your life that are a little worried about you.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>They are?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Super worried. It has come to my attention that you are smack bang in the middle of a bully problem. And I want to say that I am so sorry I didn't pick up the signs earlier, Stella. I'm sorry for letting you down.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>We have a zero tolerance policy with bullying here at the school, Stella. This is serious.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Oh thank you! I've been trying to tell everyone!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="62">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Why would you tell everyone that you're a bully?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I'm not —</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>It's time to get everything out in the open. Sit down. I'm bring the others in.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>Come in please, everyone.</StageDirection>
      <StageDirection>The class enters, followed by a sheepish GREG. GREG is sniffling like he's been crying. MISS DUANE produces a small totem.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Alright, let's sit in a half circle. It hurts my heart to see such good friends involved in this, and it's a shame that Tony is off sick so he can't be a part of this, but won't it be nice for him to come back to all of his friends getting along?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I don't understand.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Well, someone needs to keep up! No judgement.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>No judgement.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Now, this is the talking totem. Whoever has this is the only one who can talk, and the rest of us listen. This is a safe space. There are no wrong things to say, but we need to respect the feelings of everyone else. Now, Greg, would you like to start? We want you to begin whatever you say with “I feel.”</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>She hands the totem to GREG. As this progresses, the totem is passed to whoever talks.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
        <Line>I feel really lonely, and I feel sad, and all I wanted to do was be your friends, and you're not letting me be your friends, and it's really hard starting at a new school because I don't know anyone and everyone is meeeeeeeaaaaaannnnn to meeeee!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="63">
      <StageDirection>He cries.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Thank you, Greg. That was really, really brave, buddy.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADISON</Speaker>
        <Line>The other day you tried to abuse my power to benefit your own interests. I just honestly feel like you've lost perspective of your own selfishness. I'm not perfect and I own that, but this is honestly such an opportunity for growth.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADDISON</Speaker>
        <Line>You're so right.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>MADYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Yeah.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Does anybody else have anything they'd like to share? Greg's pretty cool once you get to know him. Like, you just have to lighten up Stella. He roasts everyone, you don't need to be so defensive. Why can't anybody take a joke anymore? STELLA is being worn down. We're supposed to treat strangers with kindness Stella. I used to look up to you honestly.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>FOWLER</Speaker>
        <Line>This is a school that is founded on respect and trust, Stella. Lead by example.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>PRIYA takes the talking totem.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Just ... remember what we talked about.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>You know all of this is wrong.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Please. Just let it go. For all of us.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Thank you Priya. Stella, do you see how people might feel victimised by you and your behaviour?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I haven't done anything!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>It doesn't matter anymore! Just try and listen to your friends!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>You can't even listen to me!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="64">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
        <Line>Please stop fighting, I just want all of us to be friends again!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Let's turn it down, we're upsetting Greg.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>STELLA jumps up and screams. She's had enough.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Upsetting Greg?! You're all worried about Greg?! Ever since he got here, he has been nothing but be horrible to me, and nobody cares! He has said to me he wants to kill me, and hurt me, and make me feel like I'm nothing, and I have never, ever done anything to deserve it! You asked me to help him, but before I could even try, he said he was going to kill me. Before I said anything. And I feel like he will. I'm scared and I have told you so many times that I'm scared! The second my best friend thinks I've done something wrong, she leaves me. I feel like nothing. You have made me nothing! And why would anybody listen to nothing? Why won't you listen?!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>Long beat.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Someone wasn't holding the Talking Totem. I'm going to give it to you, Stella, but I won't have any more tantrums, okay? Now, what would you like to say to Greg?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>STELLA is broken. The other kids are unsettled for the first time.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I'm sorry.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>MISS DUANE applauds.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Oh my God, that's the first time that's worked! Yaaaaaay! You're friends again. Now, I need to be on hat duty. You guys go and hang out, okay?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>DUANE and PRIYA exit. A gravelly laugh from GREG.</StageDirection>
    </Page>
  </Scene>
</Script>