<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Script>
  <Scene id="scene_5_2" pageStart="64" pageEnd="66" act="Act 5: The Showdown" title="The Quad" description="Greg challenges Stella to a fight at the flagpole">
    <Page number="64">
      <SceneHeading>The Quad</SceneHeading>
    </Page>
    <Page number="65">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
        <Line>Dirt, or water?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Leave me alone.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
        <Line>Answer the question. Dirt or water?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I don't even know what you mean.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
        <Line>It's funny what happens to a human body in the water. It sustains the creatures of the ocean. The fish will feed on your eyes, your tongue, your skin. Even your bones will be given to the ocean. And there's nothing you can do.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>STELLA takes a deep breath. With no confidence:</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I'll fight you.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
        <Line>What?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>If I have to fight you, that's what I'll do.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>GREG advances on her.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
        <Line>Good.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Tomorrow. 3 o'clock, at the flagpole. That's where we'll fight. The whole school will be able to see then.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
        <Line>You better show up. If you don't, I'll find you wherever you are and we'll fight anyway. And trust me — you don't want that to happen. What's that on your shirt?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>STELLA looks down and GREG punches her, hard in the stomach. She is winded. GREG is laughing. All of the kids see this and do nothing.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
        <Line>I learned that one today. It's hilarious. I did it to a dog this morning. He had no idea what was on his shirt! It was awesome. What now, pussy? You going to cry? You going to have a little cry? Humans are so gross, dude.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="66">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>GREG</Speaker>
        <Line>Enjoy your last night on earth. Tomorrow, 3 o'clock, flagpole. That's where you die.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>He leaves. STELLA starts sobbing. MISS DUANE enters.</StageDirection>
    </Page>
  </Scene>
</Script>