<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Script>
  <Scene id="scene_1_3" pageStart="14" pageEnd="21" act="Act 1: The Inciting Incident" title="The Quad" description="Stella, Tony, and Priya discuss holidays and toilet licking">
    <Page number="14">
      <StageDirection>The middle of the school yard. The start of a new term, new year. STELLA is sitting in the yard with TONY. TONY is eating M&amp;Ms.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>... So then I went to stay with my Dad for the rest of the holidays, and there's like this huge BMX track out the back of his house, and these kids ride there every Saturday and I saw this big kid break his arm and the bone was sticking out and everything and he was and then we had KFC. So holidays were good I guess.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Ive never seen your dad before.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>He's not around here much. He lives closer up near the bay. Like past the movies. The cheap one, not the good one.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Is he cool?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Uh yeah. He buys me KFC and then he leaves me on my own to do whatever for like the whole weekend. He's like the perfect Dad.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Did you wash your school uniform.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>You don't have to. They're like jeans.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Um, wow. Who told you that?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Dad. He also said hed teach me how to do a sleeper hold for my birthday.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>On you?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>I dunno. He didn't say.</Line>
        <Line>What did you do on the holidays?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I played Overwatch mostly.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>I've already beaten it.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="15">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>You can't beat it Overwatch. That's not the point.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Well I did. Yew.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>PRIYA runs in.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>You guys! Dakota said that Aaron Anderson just licked a seat in the boys' toilet for 2 dollars and it was rank and now his breath smells like toilet duck.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Priya, what? Why? Why are you telling us?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>It was awesome.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Once I saw a guy lick a dead body for twenty cents.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Your stories are such BS Tony. Leave them in Grade 9 with flossing. Nobody does it anymore. And you need to stop eating so much sugar.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>You're not my mum.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>I dont have to be to tell you what you eat is straight up killing you.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Not even. I actually feel stronger. My cousin once ate a whole box of LCM's and he was able to slow down time.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Tony, your cousin was lying. You can't bend time by ealing sugar.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>You can. Jack said he was able to move so fast people couldn't even see him anymore.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>People saw him running around the Rebel Sport screaming without pants. My sister was working and she said they had to throw out the yoga mats.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>It's not healthy.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Licking a toilet would be better for you.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="16">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>You know for the smartest Grade Tenner you're still pretty dumb, Priya. You can't argue with something my cousin said.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>I am the smartest Grade Tenner. I'm taking a uni class this year.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Well I can jump and touch the top of doors. We all have stuff we're good at.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>I bet you'd lick the toilet seat for one dollar.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Priya, don't. You know he will, stop encouraging him.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>I'm not encouraging him, he's just following his own pattern of behaviour. Risk and reward. It's important for him to learn and reflect so he can change. And he'll lick pee so it's funny. Won't you?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>TONY thinks about it.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Show me the dollar.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>PRIYA does. TONY and her shake hands.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Tony, you're in Grade 10 now. We've gone through a lot of growth over the holidays. Don't undo it.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>It's fine. Aaron licked it first, so it's clean. I know what I'm doing.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I don't think it works like that.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Takea selfie of you doing it. 'm not going in there. It smells from across the school. Why does every boy's toilet just smell so specific?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>This is going to be the best year ever!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>TONY runs off to lick the toilet. TYSON skates in.</StageDirection>
    </Page>
    <Page number="17">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Hey gronk. Mum texted me to say I had to give you lunch. You left before I could.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>She could've done it herself.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>She left for work early. You weren't up.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Youre going to get a uniform warning again with those shoes.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Let them. I'm here, I got myself and I got you here. If they want to warn me that's fine. Their choice to be petty. You get your teachers yet?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Yes, thank you Tyson, you can go now. Not a baby.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Yeah alright Grade 10s. You know you're in the invisible year, right? You're like the middle aged child of the school. Stuff gets weird in Grade 10. Watch out.</Line>
        <Line>Hey Priya.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>PRIYA shrinks.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>UhyeahheyTyson.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>How's your sister?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Yeahgood</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>She mention me at all?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>NoIdunnoshe'sdumbwhatever.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>I thought she enjoyed the movie. Tell her I said hey, okay?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>YeahalrightIwill.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TYSON</Speaker>
        <Line>Sweet. Stay gold, big kids.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>He skates away.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Did my brother and your sister go on a date?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>He came to my house. Where I live.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Oh my god.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="18">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>And my mum and dad weren't home and Sonam and him were on the couch and let's just say I'm glad I had my headphones in.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>UGGH I've got a mental image!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>That gave me a mental image!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Ewwwwwwww</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Ewwwwwwww</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>We'd be related if they got married.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>We could do adult things together like have brunch and complain about tax. Hey.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Let's have each other's back this year, okay? If Tyson's right we might just need to hang on a bit.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Yeah, for sure. I think we'll be fine. This is going to be a big year.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>KID [off] Oi Tonksie what're you doing? Tonksie!</StageDirection>
      <StageDirection>Offstage, sounds of disgust and horror from near the toilet blocks. TONY appears.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>I did it. I filmed it and everything. I'm the winner.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>That's not what Id call you.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>She throws him the dollar. MISS DUANE, the Grade Ten Bio teacher, enters.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Tony Tonks, get over here now.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>What? I do?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Whenever I hear screaming in the quad I know you'll have something to do with it. Do I really have to tell you that licking a toilet isn't the kind of behaviour that we expect from you?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>But Priya said shed give me a dollar if] did it.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="19">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>I didn't think hed actually do it. I lost a dollar. I'm the victim!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Well, you can talk about it with each other in detention later today.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Miss!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Miss!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>MISS DUANE pulls out her detention slips.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>On the first day, too. That's a red hot record. Let's see... Tony Tonks, Priya Pingali, and Stella Bunt.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>What? I didn't do anything!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>You were here too. Why didn't you stop it?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I don't know.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>And when these two were making a bet about putting a tongue on a toilet, where did you go?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Nowhere. I was here.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>So you saw your friends doing something wrong and you did nothing. What if Tony gets sick? How are you going to feel then knowing you could have stopped it? What if he dies? What if he gets blood poisoning and the last thing he ever hears is the sound of his own rattling chest as he tries to keep alive, not ever sure as to why he even wants to be alive and in so much agony? What'll you do then miss?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>Can that happen?</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I tried to tell him —</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>You better learn to assert yourself, miss, or people will walk all over you. One minute your friend is licking toilets, the next thing your partner is distant and you drive to school one morning with the handbrake on because you were too distracted trying to do your makeup in the mirror because you woke up late because you were up all night writing the erotic novel that'll be your ticket out of your here because you cannot deal with that bell and whatever song Janine in the front office likes this week.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
    <Page number="20">
      <StageDirection>The school bell rings. It's a terrible song — something like Brave by Sara Bareilles.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Great, there goes my break. Let's make it detention for the rest of the week.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>ALL</Speaker>
        <Line>NO!</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>This afternoon after school. I'll have some jobs for you. Now off to assembly. And no more licking things. We haven't had a quarantine since the peanut outbreak at the school musical and I'm not going back there again. Assembly. Now.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>MISS DUANE goes.</StageDirection>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Thanks a lot, you butt munch! You got me into trouble.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>She's right, Stella. You can be so irresponsible.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>I think you can look after yourself, Tony.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>TONY</Speaker>
        <Line>It's not my fault ''m impulsive. I'm a spring baby. You really dropped the ball on this one.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>PRIYA</Speaker>
        <Line>Dont blame her! Oh God. This is bad. This is really bad.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>STELLA</Speaker>
        <Line>Look, it's not a big deal. We'll just go to detention and that'll be it. At least we're doing it together.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
      <StageDirection>MISS DUANE appears again as the other students scatter onstage to sit for assembly.</StageDirection>
    </Page>
    <Page number="21">
      <DialogueBlock >
        <Speaker>DUANE</Speaker>
        <Line>Guys. Thank you. Move. Jordan! Stop running. Straight lines please.</Line>
      </DialogueBlock>
    </Page>
  </Scene>
</Script>